我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For 5 years,I was stranded on survive.
an island with only one goal--
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish--
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and bring down those who
are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
- 妈妈
- 是Sarah的事
- Mom?
- It's about Sarah.
- 她怎么了
- 我觉得她可能还活着
- What about her?
- I think she may be alive.
我不是来伤害你或者你父亲的
I'm not here to hurt you or your father.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I trust you?!
因为你一直相信
Because you always have.
这是我女儿 Helena
This is my daughter,Helena.
她父亲杀了她的未婚夫后
When her father killed her fiancé,
她就变得阴暗扭曲
she changed into
something dark and twisted.
我一个人在仇恨中太久了
I have been alone in
my hate for so long.
- 这算什么
- 报仇
- What is this?
- Payback.
警方已经扣押他了 他终会入狱的
The police have him in custody. He's
going to jail and then onto prison.
我不会停止的
I'm not going to stop.
先生 要跳舞吗
Hey,mister. You feel like a dance?
当然
Absolutely.
这是你的初夜吗
Tonight your first night?
第一次也是最后一次 Gus
First,and last. Gus.
- Helena
- 我在找我父亲
- Helena!
- I'm looking for my father.
我想会知道他的下落的只有律师了
I figure if anybody knows where
he is,it'd be his attorney.
我不知道
I don't.
Helena 我发誓
Helena,I swear...
我可以告诉你FBI把Frank留哪了
I'd tell you where the
FBI's keeping Frank,
但我和你爸出证认罪交易后
but after your father and I
made his plea deal to testify,
他们就什么都不告诉我了
the Feds,they stopped
telling me anything.
求你 一定要相信我
Please. You have to believe me.
我相信
I do.
贵宾室
vip**
Gus 音乐都结束了 你还在里面吗
Hey,Gus,song's over,man.
You still in there?
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 Ducky 旖旎
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:卡灰
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
Sync: 卡灰
绿箭侠
第一季 第十七集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
arrow
S01E17
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
天哪 这地方太棒了
Oh,my gosh! It looks amazing!
是啊
Yeah.
Steve Aoki会做DJ 在那
Steve Aoki's going to
deejay. Right there.
- 什么 你怎么搞定他的
- 我约过他妹妹
- What? How did you get Steve Aoki?
- I dated his sister.
- 很久以前的事了
- 好吧
- A million years ago,a million years ago.
- Ok.
明晚做我的舞伴好吗
So,will you be my date tomorrow night?
- 参加俱乐部开张算是正式约会吗
- 我当然希望如此
- Is a club opening a proper date?
- I certainly hope so.
- 这是答应了吗
- 不是
- Is that a "yes?"
- No.
这才是
That's a "yes."
Laurel 很高兴你打来电话
Laurel. I'm glad you called.
发生了这么多事
我们俩很久没说过话了
Too much... It's too long
for us to go without talking.
爸 我得告诉你些事
Dad,I have
to tell you--
不 等等 在你说之前我必须得道歉
No,no,listen,before you say
anything,I got to apologize.
我不该利用你去抓弓箭手 对不起
I should never have used you to
catch the archer,and I'm sorry.
Laurel 真的很对不起
Laurel,I'm
just-- I'm sorry.
谢谢 我也欠你一个道歉
Thank you. I owe you an apology,too.
为什么
For what?
你好 Quentin
Hello,Quentin.
你还好吗 看上去不错
How are you? You look well.
你怎么来了 你来干什么
What are you doing here?
Why-- why are you here?
我来这是因为我相信Sarah还活着
I'm here because I believe
Sarah's still alive.
什么
What?!
- 爸 坐下吧
- 怎么回事
- Dad. Sit-- -
What is going on?
听妈说吧 坐下
Just hear mom out. Sit.
怎么回事
What's going on?
从头说起吧
Start from the beginning.
Oliver是在中国北海的
炼狱岛上被发现的
Oliver was found on an island called Lian Yu in the North China Sea.
那一带有成千上百座荒岛
There are hundreds; Thousands of
deserted islands in this chain.
如果Sarah也幸存下来了呢
What if Sarah had survived,too?
没人知道她是不是被冲上这些岛了
And nobody would know if she'd
washed up in any one of those.
其实你没有证据证明她还活着
So you don't actually have
any proof that she's alive?
我有
I have proof.
这是一个游客拍的
A tourist took this.
- 说不定是别人
- 她不像Sarah吗
- Could be anybody.
- Doesn't it look just like Sarah?
我们的女儿还活着 Quentin
Our daughter's a survivor,Quentin.
你这算什么
Ah,you have some nerve.
三年了 没有电话
没有邮件 什么都没有
Three years,no phone
calls,no emails,nothing.
- 就突然拿张照片出现在我面前
- 爸 别这样
- You just show up with an
old photo-- - Dad,please.
不 你听我说
Sarah在那次事故中已经死了
No. Please,you listen to
me,ok? Sarah died on that boat.
我不会相信的
why are you making me re-live this? I'm not doing this.
- 爸
- 别
- Dad...
- No.
我和Chris还有Shane说了
So I told Chris and Shane
他们可以做我们的舞伴
出席Oliver的俱乐部开张
they could be our plus ones
tonight to Oliver's club--
如果他们运气好的话
if they're lucky.
我们都能带伴儿的吧
We both have plus ones,right?
我不知道 你等我一下
Uh,I-I don't know.
Hang on just a second.
小偷也会喝咖啡休息呀
I didn't know purse
snatchers took coffee breaks.
对于骄傲自大的白富美来说
You know,for a stuck up,rich bitch,
你也花太多时间在林中空地了吧
you seem to spend a lot
of time here in the Glades.
- 我在这工作
- 你 会有工作
- My job's around here.
- You? Have a job?
没错 你也试着找份工作吧
Yeah. You know,you
should try it some time.
不要老在街上游荡抢别人钱包了
Instead of hanging waiting to boost somebody's handbag.
out on a street corner,
听上去不错 但是谁会要一个
Sounds good. Know anyone who's hiring high
school dropouts with a couple of priors,
有前科 无推荐
还有暴力史的高中辍学生呢
no references and a history of violence?
我也许会
Actually,I might.
你知道林中空地开了家
叫翡翠的新俱乐部吧
You know that new club
opening in the Glades? Verdant?
我哥开的 他好像在请候客服务生
My brother owns it. I think he
might be hiring valet attendants.
你觉得这样好吗
让我去负责陌生人的车
Do you think it's a good idea?
Me,taking the keys to stranger's cars?
要么接受要么闭嘴
I think it's time you put up or shut up.
找你哥谈
Talk to your brother.
你去哪了
Where you been?
我让自己难得享受了一个早晨
Oh,I thought I'd give
myself a rare morning in.
别这样看我 俱乐部终于要开张了
Don't look at me like that.
The club is opening,finally.
McKenna和我今晚是第六次约会
McKenna and I are going on date
number six tonight,which is...
意义非凡 我不知道
It's significant. And,uh,I don't know.
今天暂且放过那些恶人
It seemed like a good day
to give the bad guys a rest.
我在担心这个坏姑娘
Well,it's the bad girls
that I'm worried about.
Helena
Helena.
是的 我喜欢叫她你的前精神病女友
Yes,or as I like to call
her,your psycho ex-girlfriend.
这是在猫巷 脱衣舞夜总会
This was taken at Alley
Cats,the strip joint.
警方告示死者是Gus Sabatoni
The police report lists the
stiff's name as Gus Sabatoni.
他是Bertinelli的律师
That's Bertinelli's lawyer.
她来斯特林市找他干什么
Why would she come back to
Starling City just for him?
他貌似没有尽职
It's not like he did a good job.
她父亲在服无期徒刑 不能假释
Her father's serving consecutive
life sentences without parole.
得了Oliver
我们都清楚这只是时间问题
Come on,Oliver,we both knew
this was just a matter of time.
你试着帮过她 但不行
You tried to help her,you couldn't.
现在的问题是
Now the only question is,
她还要多久会来找我们
how long before she drops the dime
on you,me,this whole operation.
我要你联系她在黑手党里的线人
Look,I want you to get in touch
with her contacts in the Bratva.
随便问谁 查出她在哪 为什么回来
Talk to anyone on the street, figure
out where Helena is,why she's back.
行 不过Oliver
Ok. But
Oliver--
Dig 她回来肯定有原因
dig,if she's here,she's
here for a reason.
如果不是因为Frank Bertinelli
我们也得查出她在密谋什么
If that's not Frank Bertinelli, we
need to know what she has planned.
好
Ok.
- 飞毛腿
- 我们在这
- Speedy?
- Oh,we're in here.
看看谁回来了
Look who's back.
她在跟我说你们在鲁索的第一次约会
She was just telling me about
your guys' first date-- at Russo's.
好啊 Oliver
Hello,Oliver.
Ollie 我有个称不上朋友的人在找工作
Oh,Ollie,I kind of have this pseudo
friend that's looking for a job.
俱乐部还在招人吗
I was wondering if the
club's still hiring?
当然 去找Tommy吧
Yes. Of course. Talk to Tommy.
你现在就可以上楼打电话给他了
As a matter of fact,you can go
upstairs and call Tommy,right now.
好的 你真赞
Great. You rock.
你去哪了
Where you been?
巴塞罗那
Barcelona.
摩纳哥 布达佩斯
Monaco,Budapest.
我想忘了自己是谁 想忘了你
I just needed to forget who I
was. And how much I missed you.
你是想念Gus Sabatoni了吧
Do you mean like you
missed Gus Sabatoni?
Helena 我以为
你和你父亲的组织已经了断了
I thought you were done with
your father's organization,Helena.
他已被判无期徒刑
Because he's serving consecutive
life sentences in Iron Heights prison.
你复仇目的达到了
You got your revenge.
两天后 证人保护组织会给他
一个新名字 一个新生活
He just cut a deal with to testify against
the Justice Department the East Coast family.
他就永远逃离法网无迹可寻了
In 48 hours,Witness Protection a new life,and he'll be off
will give him a new name, the grid forever-- untraceable!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我父亲不该有第二次机会 第二次生命
My father doesn't deserve a
second chance-- a second life.
我一个人对付不了这么多警察
And I can't. I can't take on
a phalanx of U.S. marshals.
- 没有帮助的情况下
- 不行
- Not without help.
- No.
这是谋杀 不是伸张正义
It's murder. It's not justice.
你在这啊 今晚的开张我有个问题
Oh,there you are. I have a
question about your opening tonight.
你好
Hello.
Oliver 这是你哪个朋友
Oliver,who's your friend?
噢 妈妈 这是Helena
Helena 这是我妈
Oh! Mom,this is Helena.
Helena,this is my mother.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
- Helena正准备走
- 嗯 我要去家庭聚会了
- Helena was just leaving.
- Yes. I have a family engagement.
- 我等会过来
- 好的
- Excuse us for a minute.
- Of course.
我想我能说服你
I guess I will just have
to be more persuasive.
毕竟你也有家庭
Fortunately... You have a family,too.
翡翠
ver**
她在我家 摆明了威胁我
She was in my house. She
made a not so veiled threat.
我妈和妹妹必须严加保护
I want extra security
around my mother and sister.
- 早就想到了 兄弟
- 谢谢
- Way ahead of you,man.
- Thank you.
- 这是我的工作
- 别这种口气
- It's my job.
- For not saying,"I told you so."
长夜漫漫
Night's young.
你去哪了 俱乐部四小时后就开张了
Where you been? The
club opens in four hours.
- 我在处理供应商的事情
- 你没有
- I've been dealing with the vendors.
- No,you haven't.
Tommy 我们得谈谈
Tommy... We need to talk.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,all right.
我不说是为了保护身边的人
But I kept this a secret to protect
the people that are closest to me.
你以为我关心这个吗
Do you think that's what I care about?
是因为我被伤到了吗
What,that my feelings are hurt?
你是凶手 是杀人犯
You're a murderer. A killer.
你是我最好的朋友
可我现在完全不认识你了
You were my best friend in life, but
now it's like I don't even know you.
你说得对 我变了
You're right. I've changed.
兄弟 现在我可以向你解释
Listen,buddy,now I can explain to you.
我可以解释为什么...
I can explain to
you how and why--
有意义吗
What'd be the point?
反正我不会再信你
I wouldn't believe a word of it,anyway.
其中一枚导弹的有效射程是2400公里
One of those missiles has an effective
range of up to 2,400 kilometers.
查清Fyers的阴谋前 咱俩哪儿也不去
We're not going anywhere until we
figure out what Fyers is planning.
我猜 他要炸掉什么吧
Wild guess? He's planning
on blowing something up.
用那枚导弹 大材小用
Well,one of those could
do the job. But this?
这是发动战争的征兆
This is about starting a war.
- 跟谁打
- 有什么关系
- With who?
- What does it matter?
我们得阻止Fyers涂炭生灵
We have to stop Fyers before he
kills thousands of innocent people.
下面重兵集结呢
There are tons of soldiers down there.
即使我俩把他们都撂倒
Even if we get through all of them,
也没法偷走整套导弹发射器
we can't just steal a
whole missile launcher.
谁说要偷了
Well,who said anything
about stealing it?
那要干嘛 伏击
So what's the plan? Ambush?
不行 一次性得搞定6个人
其中肯定会有人呼叫援助
It's impossible. We can't take out all
six without one radioing for back up.
如果能把那些兵聚集在一起就好了
It'd be good if we could get
all the soldiers in one place.
不错
You're right.
破玩意儿
*****
订书机得罪你了
What'd the stapler ever do to you?
干嘛 Laurel 我忙着呢
帽衫侠的女友回来了
What is it,Laurel? I'm busy.
The Hood's girlfriend is back.
爸 早上的事 我很抱歉
Dad,I'm sorry about this morning.
可如果我据实以告
But if I told you the
real reason to come see me,
你根本不会来见我
you wouldn't have shown up.
你说得太对了
You're damn right I wouldn't.
你妈说Sarah还活在奇幻岛上
So you really believe this
garbage your mother's selling
你真相信这种胡话
about Sarah being
alive on fantasy island?
不
I mean,no.
但看一看妈妈的发现 也没什么坏处啊
But what would it hurt to take a
look at everything that mom found?
即使只是让她面对现实
Even if it's just to set her straight.
Laurel 你知不知道我花了多久
Laurel,you know how
long it's taken for me
才使自己不要每天一早就想起Sarah
to get to a place where Sarah isn't the
first thing I think about every morning?
爸...
Dad...
转告你妈 我不做任何承诺
Tell your mom I'm not
making any promises.
敬翡翠
To Verdant.
我没有一直支持这个项目
I know I haven't always been
supportive of this venture,
但我必须承认 这个夜店很赞
but I have to admit this nightclub
is quite an accomplishment.
我以你为傲 你父亲肯定也一样
I'm proud of you. Your
father would be,too.
谢谢
***
恭喜 Ollie 这儿也不是很糟啦
Yeah,congratulations,Ollie.
The club doesn't totally suck.
过奖 飞毛腿 谢谢大家来捧场
Thanks,Speedy. Thank you very
much,all of you,for coming.
你在这儿呢
There you are.
这地方真棒 我为你和Ollie自豪
This place is amazing. I'm
so proud of you and Ollie.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 你没事吧
- 我挺好
- Is everything ok?
- I'm great.
早餐真是场灾难
Well,breakfast was a disaster.
早餐 和我父母
Breakfast? With my parents?
对 今早的事
Right. That was this morning.
对不起
Sorry.
你确定没事吗 你看起来心不在焉的
Are you sure everything's ok?
Because you seem completely off.
没事 真的
I'm fine. I promise.
Tommy Tommy 你打给Roy了吗
Tommy! Tommy. Did you call Roy yet?
我给他留言了 他明天来上班
I left him a message.
He starts tomorrow.
我得去办公室看看
Which reminds me,I have to
go check in with the office.
失陪了
Excuse me.
嘿 Tommy 还记得我吗
Hey,Tommy. Remember me?
- Queen先生 打扰你一下
- 没关系 反正我又不会跳舞
- Sorry to bother you,Mr. Queen.
- Your timing is perfect. I can't dance.
他们说这个很紧急
They said it was urgent.
楼下见 立刻--Dig
meet**
- 你还好吧
- 嗯 水晶香槟快喝完了
- You ok?
- Yeah. We ran out of Cristal.
- 我去去就回
- 好
- I'll be right back.
- Ok.
Dig
Dig?
放开他 跟他无关
Let him go. He has
nothing to do with this.
我说过 Oliver 我警告过你
I told you. Oliver,I warned you.
Helena 别这样
Helena! This isn't you.
我父亲是个歹徒 凶手
My father is a mobster and a murderer.
好像你没杀过人似的
It is not like you haven't
killed men like that before!
我教过你 避免杀戮而达到目的
And I tried to teach you to obtain
your objective without killing!
通过制约别人
By applying leverage.
通过利用别人的弱点
By exploiting someone's weakness.
上面那一屋子人 我都可以抓来制约你
There is a whole club full of
leverage above our heads right now.
求你了
Please.
Oliver 别逼我做出让我们都后悔的事
Oliver,don't make me do something
that both of us will regret.
好 你赢了 我会帮你 放开他
Ok! Ok. You win. I'll
help you. Let him go.
放 开 他
Let... Him... Go!
- 别提那事
- 好
- Don't say it.
- Ok.
那就谈谈Helena吧
Then let's talk about Helena.
Oliver 如果你不是还对她有感觉的话
Oliver,if you didn't still
have feelings for this girl,
你会想出别的解决之道
you would have thought
of a different solution
而不会受她威胁去杀人
than letting her extort
you into killing someone.
你想要我怎么做
So what do you want me to do?
杀掉她吗
You want me to kill her?
你是看她长得漂亮
I think you would have a long time ago
要不你早就杀她了
if she looked like me
instead of the T-Mobile girl.
- 她是个无情的杀手 Oliver
- 她并不邪恶
- She's a stone cold killer,Oliver.
- She's not evil.
她父亲冷血地杀掉她未婚夫 她迷茫了
She's been lost since her father
killed her fiancé in cold blood.
你想冷眼旁观地说
And are you going to sit there
你不懂得复仇的欲望吗
and tell me that you don't know
what it's like to want revenge?
换了是你 会怎么做
What would you do? Hmm?
如果Floyd Lawton站在那儿
If Floyd Lawton was
standing right there?
反正不会威胁你去杀他
Nothing that will involve
blackmailing you into hunting him down.
你说对了 我是下不了手杀她
You're right. Ok? I can't kill her.
我也不能冒着泄露身份的风险
把她交给警察
And I can't take her to the police
and risk her exposing all of this.
但至少 如果我参与其中 我能控制她
But at least,if I'm involved,I
can contain her,all right?
我可以最大程度减少间接损害
I can minimize the collateral damage.
抱歉 我打扰你们了吗
Sorry,am I... interrupting something?
我们正谈起你
We were just... talking about you.
以前觉得你很不在乎我
And here I thought you
didn't care much for me.
一如既往
Still don't.
我还没找到
I haven't been able to
locate the safe house
FBI软禁你父亲的地方
where the FBI is keeping your father.
我能帮忙 我超想黑进FBI的安全系统
I can help with that. I've been dying
to hack into the FBI security system.
出去 出去
Get out. Get out.
这是私事 Felicity 请离开
This is a private
thing,Felicity. Please.
好吧
Ok.
那么 再见
See ya,I guess...
你到底有多少女朋友
How many girlfriends
do you have,exactly?
如我所说 我们没查到软禁地址
Like I said... We don't
know where the safe house is.
我们只知道今晚
What we do know is that the Marshall
service is taking your father
法警要带你父亲去司法部的听证会
to a hearing at the
Justice Department tonight.
有个问题 Helena
There's a problem... Helena.
有两辆车 其中一辆是诱饵
There are two vans. And
one of them's a decoy.
我们也有两个人啊
Well,it's a good thing
there's two of us,then.
现在取消行动 为时未晚
It's not too late to call this off.
你了解我的
I think you know me better than that.
我不让他坐牢
I don't take prisoners.
我巡视的时候发现这家伙
I found an intruder while I
was circling the perimeter.
是Wilson
It's Wilson.
你杀了我好几个朋友 混蛋
You killed a few of my
friends,you son of a bitch.
那我再杀几个
And I'm going to kill a few more.
我先跟我们的律师谈谈
然后叫他们给你回电
I'll talk to one of our lawyers
and have them call you right back.
刮胡子弄伤了
Cut yourself shaving?
- 能聊会儿吗
- 可以
- You got a minute?
- Sure.
- Roy第一天表现如何
- 那小子没来
- How was Roy's first day?
- Kid never showed.
我过来是想为昨晚的事道歉
I just,uh,I came by to
apologize for last night.
比起道歉 我更想知道实情
Instead of an apology,why
don't you try the truth?
你可以从腕伤谈起
You can start with your wrist.
我在夜店跟一个搅局的打了一架
I got into a fight with
a blender at the club.
挺二的
It was stupid.
我以为你会说实话
I thought I asked for the truth.
肯定发生什么事了 为什么不告诉我
I know something's up. Why won't
you tell me what's going on?
- 我不能说
- 为什么
- Because I can't.
- Why not?
这个我也不能说 我真希望可以告诉你
I can't tell you that,either.
I wish that I could.
Laurel 对不起
Laurel,I'm sorry.
我也是
So am I.
现在我真的很需要你 Tommy
I really need you right now,Tommy.
我妈跑来跟我说我姐没死
My mother shows up saying my
dead sister is still alive,
我听信了她 我爸因此发飙了
and my father is furious with me
that I'm even listening to her.
我真不知该信谁了
And I don't know who to believe.
- 我快崩溃了
- 我在你身边呢
- I feel like I'm falling apart.
- I'm still here for you.
不 你没有 你人在心不在
No. You're not. You're
a million miles away,
最糟的是 我不知这是为何
and the worst part is,I
don't even know why.
对不起
I'm sorry.
跟踪我哈
Wow. Stalker much?
我给你找了份工作 你却没来上班
You didn't show up
for the job I got you.
我改主意了 不想帮你哥停宾利车
Yeah,I had second thoughts about
parking your brother's Bentley.
怎么 当泊车的跌份儿吗
What,being a valet is beneath you?
不 接受富家女的施舍才跌份儿
No,but accepting charity
from some rich girl is.
我是有钱人 为什么会让你如此反感
Why are you so obsessed with
the fact that I have money?
金钱不是万能的
You know,money isn't everything.
果然是有钱人的口吻
Spoken like someone who's got it.
失陪了 我得回到我的罪恶人生了
Now,uh,if you'll excuse me,I need
to get back to my life of crime.
喂 帮个忙 我迷路了
Yo,can you help me out? Think I'm lost.
- 市中心怎么走
- 我 我不知道
- Where's downtown at?
- I-- I-- I don't know.
给我们指个道 给点钱更棒
Maybe you can give us some
directions. Or better yet,some money--
你没事吧
You ok?
你在流血
You're bleeding!
被刺了一刀当然会流血
Yeah,that's what happens
when you get stabbed.
只杀父亲
Just your father.
让其他人受伤的话 我会赏你一箭
Anyone else gets hurt and
I'll put an arrow in you.
真贴心
That's sweet.
总算知道你是怎么
迷倒你的警察女友了
Now I know how you charmed
your cop girlfriend.
把Frank Bertinelli交给我
Give me Frank Bertinelli.
你父亲不在这辆车上
Your father's not in the van.
但他托我问候你
But he sends his regards.
帽衫侠在哪儿
Where's the Hood?
Helena Bertinelli
Helena Bertinelli...
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
糟糕
Damn it.
但你所说的一切都将成为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be
held against you in a court of law.
你有权请律师
You have the right to an attorney.
Paul Copani
Nick Salvati  Gus Sabatoni
Paul Copani,Nick Salvati,Gus Sabatoni.
你是个不错的猎手 Bertinelli小姐
You are quite the hunter,Ms. Bertinelli.
我应该说"女猎手"
Well,I guess I should
make that "Huntress."
你有计划地干掉了
你父亲的犯罪集团中的每个人
You've been systemically taking down everyone
in your father's criminal organization.
Gus Sabatoni死的时候
When Gus Sabatoni turned up dead,
我们就知道 你弑父是迟早的事
we knew it was just a matter of time
before you tried to murder your old man.
- 想告诉我们为什么吗
- 不太想
- Do you want to tell us why?
- Not particularly.
你该再考虑下
You should reconsider.
我们抓住了你
但特警队没来得及抓住义务警员
We got you,but the vigilante got
away before E.S.U. could move on him.
你知道他是谁 他的真实身份 对不
You know who he is. Who
he really is. Don't you?
Bertinelli小姐 你已经失踪一天了
这事实无法改变
Ms. Bertinelli,you're going away
for all day,we can't change that.
但事情可以就此变好 或是变糟
But things can be better.
Or they could be worse.
告诉我他是谁 我会尽力让事情变好
You tell me his name,I will do
everything I can to make it better.
Oliver Queen
Oliver Queen.
你在跟他约会 对不
You're dating him now,right?
昨晚我看到你在他俱乐部开业典礼上
I saw you at the opening
of his club last night.
他跟你说过我们曾是恋人吗
Did he mention that
we used to be lovers?
我们想知道帽衫侠的事
不是Oliver Queen
We want to know about
the Hood,not Oliver Queen.
我告诉你个小秘密
Let me let you in
on a little secret--
你俩成不了的
it's not going to work
out between you two.
Oliver有特殊的才能
You see,Oliver has a particular talent.
他会利用人
He uses people.
他利用了我 利用了警探您的女儿
He used me,he used the
detective here's daughter--
不好意思 是女儿们
excuse me--
daughters.
要是我 就会全身而退
I would get out of it
before you get yourself hurt.
给你最后一次机会
Last chance.
说出他的名字
His name.
帽衫侠
The Hood.
- 什么情况
- 不知道 快走
- What's going on?
- I don't know. ***
走 离开这
Go,get out of here!
快出门
Head for a door.
别动
Freeze!
可是次冒险援救啊
Sounds like quite the daring rescue.
你有Roy这个朋友 很幸运 Thea
You're very lucky to have
a friend like Roy,Thea.
- 我还不知道么
- 我们不是朋友
- Oh,don't I know it.
- We're not friends.
让我帮你缝合
Well,let me get you stitched up,
你俩再决定是啥关系
and then you two can decide
what you are or aren't.
你真混蛋
You are such a jerk.
Roy 怎么了
Roy. What's a matter?
没事 我觉得我不需要打针
Nothing. I just don't
see why I need a shot.
别告诉我你这黑帮硬汉
Oh,don't tell me a tough
gang banger like yourself
还怕小小的针头
is afraid of a tiny little needle.
看起来可不小
It doesn't look so tiny.
想想别的 别去想针头
Well,just think about something
else. Besides the needle.
想什么
Like what?
这可能会有点疼
Ok,now this could sting a little.
好了
Done.
也不是很糟 对吧
Now that wasn't so bad,was it?
谢谢你救了我
Thanks for the save.
我可不能冒你跟警察坦白的风险
I couldn't risk you
telling the police about me.
就这原因吗
Is that the only reason?
为什么你不能承认
Why can't you just admit...
你也还对我有感觉
That you still have feelings for me,too?
这是什么
What is it?
去罗马的机票
A plane ticket to Rome,
和护照 你能在别处开始新生活
and a passport so you can
start a new life somewhere else.
警察知道你在追查你父亲 Helena
The police know you're
tracking your father,Helena.
你不会找到他的
You'll never find him.
所以离开我的城市吧
So get out of my city.
把这些放在发射台周围
Place these around the launcher.
动作快 后援随时会到
Do it quickly. Their backup
will be arriving any second.
还有1分钟抵达发射台
We're 60 seconds out from the launcher.
放好后 就炸掉它
Set your final charges
and we'll blow it.
我有个更好的注意
I think I have a better idea.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我在取电路板
I'm taking the circuit board.
没它电脑和发射台都无法运行
Computers won't work without
them,and neither will this.
筹码
Leverage.
抱歉 我应该先打电话的
I'm sorry. I should have called.
没事 请进
No,it's-- it's
ok. Come on in.
- 你确定吗
- 嗯
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,yeah.
- 谢谢
- 我很惊讶 但很开心
- Thank you.
- I'm surprised,but I'm happy.
- 是吗
- 嗯
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
没事吧
Everything ok?
难熬的一晚啊
I had a really rough night.
我没想到 我的工作 还有俱乐部
I just wasn't anticipating,with
my work and the club,
我觉得我让大家失望了
I feel like I'm letting everybody down.
我家人 Tommy 还有你
My family and Tommy and... You.
我觉得我让你失望了
I feel like I'm letting you down.
你对自己太苛刻了 对工作要求很高
You're being too hard on yourself.
We both have demanding jobs.
但也不能伤害你亲近的人
That's no excuse for hurting
the people closest to you.
没错 但你坚信自己所做的事
No,but when you believe in what you do,
你会想办法成功的
you find a way to make it work.
怎么做
How?
那...
Well...
要做的第一件事
The first thing you do
是找到一个永不须道歉的人
is you find yourself someone
you never have to apologize to.
Settle down with me
* Settle down with me *
cover me up
* cover me up *
lie down with me
* lie down with me *
and hold me
* and hold me *
in your arms
* in your arms *
Your heart's against my chest
* Your heart's against my chest *
your lips pressed in my neck
* your lips pressed in my neck *
I'm falling for your eyes
* I'm falling for your eyes *
but they don't know me yet
* but they don't know me yet *
And with a feeling I'll forget
* And with a feeling I'll forget *
是我 我在进行多任务处理
拦截了警方报告
Hey,it's me. I was multitasking,and
intercepted a police report.
当地的体育用品商店
被弓箭手打劫
A local sporting goods store just got
robbed of one high powered cross bow.
是这样...
Now...
不是巧合 就是你的神经病前女友
Could be a crazy coincidence
or your psycho ex-girlfriend--
Dig说的 不是我 还在城里
Dig's words,not mine--
is still in town.
有新情况会告诉你
I'll let you know if
I learn anything more.
期间...小心点
In the meantime,just... watch your back.
今早我们没好好认识下
I don't think we had a chance to
be properly introduced this morning.
- Felicity
- Oliver Oliver...
- Felicity?
- Oliver. Oliver...
我在这
I'm here.
你没事吧
You ok?
我接到了电话 怎么了
I got your call. What happened?
Helena
Helena.
她想知道她爸所在的安全屋地址
She wanted the address to the safe
house where her father's being kept.
她让我黑入FBI数据库
She made me hack the FBI database.
抱歉 Oliver
Sorry,Oliver.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
Oliver 你要怎么做
Oliver,what are you going to do?
我本该做的事
What I should have
done in the first place.
Helena
Helena!
三级警报 Bertinelli安全屋发生枪击
Code three,shots fired at
the Bertinelli safe house.
我是Hall 已到现场
This is Hall. I'm onsite.
等待后援 警探 这是命令
Wait for back-up,Detective.
That's an order.
你不会杀我的
You won't shoot me.
你不是杀手 记得吗
You're not a murderer. Remember?
但你是
But you are.
如果我放你走
这些人的死 就是我的责任
And if I let you go,that
blood will be on my hands.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我练过这招
I practiced that move.
我觉得我有天会用到
I had a feeling I might need it someday.
你本会杀掉我的
You would have killed me.
够了
Enough!
别动
Freeze!
放下 慢慢转身
Put it down. Turn around. Slowly.
不
No!
McKenna
McKenna?
你怎么样
How you feeling?
很麻
Uh,numb.
- 别...别动
- 好
- Hey,don't--
don't move. - Ok.
我见过了你的医生 他很不错
I met your doctor. He's a nice guy.
他说你还活着 很幸运
He says you're lucky to be alive.
他还说我股骨粉碎性骨折
Yeah. He also said I
have a shattered femur,
至少一年才能恢复
and it's going to take
at least a year to rehab.
- 我喜欢当警察
- 拜托
- I loved being a cop.
- Oh,come on.
McKenna 你还是警察
McKenna. You're still a cop.
再一场手术 就能回家了
You have one more
surgery,go home--
- 我不回家
- 怎么了
- I'm not going home.
- What?
我要搬去海滨城 和我姐住
I'm moving to Coast City
to live with my sister.
那有本国最先进的理疗设备
They have the best physical therapy
facility in the country there.
我会去看你的
I'll visit.
- 我是个亿万富翁 对不
- 对
- Hey,I'm a billionaire,right?
- Yeah.
我也搬去海滨城
I'll move to Coast City.
你真好 但...你的俱乐部刚开业
That's very sweet,but...
Your club just opened.
你的工作在这
And your work is here.
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
担心你是我的责任
It's my responsibility
to worry about you.
别再担心了 好么
Just stop,ok?
听着 你知道我对你的感觉
Listen,you know how I feel about you.
别再难上加难了
Please don't make this
harder than it already is.
好吧
Ok. Ok.
你需要什么就说
It's,uh,it's whatever you need.
M. HALL警探
det**
- 你在清理你的桌子吗
- 不 朋友的
- Are you cleaning out your desk?
- No. A friend's.
你找我
You asked to see me.
- 坐吧
- 好
- Why don't you take a seat.
- Ok.
我准备好听你说了
I'm ready to listen now.
谢谢
Thank you.
我听说了McKenna的事 你还好吗
I,uh,heard about McKenna. You ok?
不太好
Not really.
听着 我知道我最近很混蛋
Look,I know that I
have been a jerk lately.
我只是不明白
你怎么能对我隐瞒这个大秘密
I just couldn't understand how you
could keep such a huge secret from me.
但我从没想过你为此所牺牲的
But I-- I never considered
the toll it must take on you.
对亲近的人说谎
Lying to the people
that are closest to me.
这是最难的
It's the hardest part.
我明白
I get that.
我之前错了...
I was wrong...
以为我可以有双重身份
to think that I could have it both ways;
能做我要做的
that I could do what I do
还能过正常的生活
and still have a normal life.
不为人所知
With anyone.
除非孑身一人 不然不会开心
Except if you're alone,you're
never going to be happy.
或许不是这样
Maybe not.
但我开心 不是最重要的事
But me being happy isn't
what's important right now.
你的计划 你做主
Your plan,your call.
Fyers
Fyers.
Queen先生 我知道你会联系我
Mr. Queen. I thought I
might be hearing from you.
电路板在我们手里
We have the circuit board.
你这是自掘坟墓
You're making a grave mistake.
我的人正在搜查这座岛
My men are scouring the
island for you as we speak.
他们找到你 会杀了你
And when they find
you,they will kill you.
恐怕是慢慢折磨死
Very slowly,I'm afraid.
如果你的人杀了我们
你就别想拿到电路板了
If your men kill us,then you'll
never find the circuit board.
在那之后 你我都明白
And after that,we both know
that all you'll be left with
你手中就只有一团废铁
is a really ugly piece of modern art.
你想怎样
What do you propose?
做笔交易
A trade.
明白了 想拿什么交换
I see. And what do you want in exchange?
离岛
I want a way off the island.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
arrow
S01E17
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo